There's Always Been Something Between Them.
Always Be My Maybe is a romance, comedy film directed by Nahnatchka Khan.
Reunited after 15 years, famous chef Sasha and hometown musician Marcus feel the old
sparks of attraction, but struggle to adapt to each other's worlds.
Marcus, played by Randall Park.
Veronica, played by Michelle Buteau.
Keanu Reeves, played by Keanu Reeves.
Chloe, played by Casey Wilson.
Sasha, played by Ali Wong.
Harry, played by James Saito.
Always Be My Maybe is a 2019 American romantic comedy film, written by Ali Wong,
Randall Park and Michael Golamco and directed by Nahnatchka Khan.
It stars Park and Wong as childhood friends Marcus and Sasha, who have
not been in touch since a brief teenage fling ended badly.
When Sasha returns to San Francisco to open a restaurant and romantic chemistry from their teenager years remains,
Marcus' fears and Sasha's fame and demanding career challenge their potential new relationship.
James Saito, Michelle Buteau, Vivian Bang, Daniel
Dae Kim and Keanu Reeves also star.
The film was released in select theaters on May 29,
2019, and on Netflix on May 31, 2019.
The film explores themes of new york city, san francisco,
california, restaurant owner, widower, childhood friends.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.